Guide to the Shoot II Films collection, 2000-2004 MS 657
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Too Short collection
2000-2004
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Garrett, Corey
MS 657
0.5 Linear Feet (1 box)
VHS tapes, mini-DV tapes, magazines, contracts, and correspondence of Too Short (Todd Anthony Shaw)
Biographical Note
Todd Anthony Shaw (born April 28, 1966), better known by the stage name Too Short (stylized as Too $hort), is an American rapper, producer, and actor. He is best known for his hit songs like "The Ghetto" and "Blow the Whistle". Too Short is one of the very few musicians to have been able to collaborate with both TuPac and The Notorious B.I.G. during the height of their careers. Too Short released two films as well, 2001's Too Short Uncensored and Titty City.
Scope and Contents
VHS tapes, mini-DV tapes, magazines, contracts, and correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was donated by Corey Garrett to Rice University through the Center for Engaged Research and Collaborative Learning (CERCL) in 2016.
Related Materials
A listing of CERCL (Center for Engaged Research and Collaborative Learning) archival collections is available: http://libguides.rice.edu/CERCL
Index Terms
Subjects
Music; Rap (Music); Periodicals; African Americans; Motion picture industry
Document Types
videotapes; contracts
Subjects (Persons)
Garrett, Corey; Too Short (Musician)
- Series I: Contracts, Correspondence, Printed Material, 2000-2004
  - Licensing Agreement (Shoot II Films and Todd Shaw) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Email correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Zomba Recording Corporation contract, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Too Short Distribution Agreement, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Distribution sheets (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Platinum magazine, September-October 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rap Pages magazine, November 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - XXL magazine, January-February 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - XXL magazine, March 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Video
  - T*tty City VHS tape (Box 1)
  - Too Short "Uncensored:Nationwide Behind the Scenes" VHS tape, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Unedited Willie Hutch interview VHS tape (Box 1)
  - Pimpin Ken VHS tape (Box 1)
  - Astroworld/Bad Wayz footage/Redman concert VHS tape (Box 1)
  - Short and Breed PhatTrax VHS tape (Box 1)
  - Unedited T*tty City Raw footage, five mini DV tapes (Box 1)